# Kae Unterseher

## Full Stack Developer

#### SUMMARY

Highly proficient programmer with 5+ years of experience building websites and applications professionally, as well 7+ years of providing college-level CS instruction. Very adaptable and dedicated to writing code that is clean, efficient, and well-documented.

### **LANGUAGES & LIBRARIES**

Frontend: Javascript (jQuery, React), CSS (LESS, SCSS, Tailwind), HTML (semantic elements)

**Server Side:** Node.js (Express, Next.js, Handlebars), Python (Django), PHP (WordPress, Magento), C# (ASP.NET)

Databases: SQL (MySQL, sqlite, PostgreSQL), MongoDB

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2018 - Present I Wyzant, Inc

#### **Tutor**

- Five-star rated tutor to nearly 800 students learning HTML, CSS, PHP, Python, and Javascript.
- Explained beginner, intermediate, and advanced concepts in one-on-one remote sessions with students from a wide range of learning experience and personal backgrounds.
- Wrote example code to illustrate various concepts, including recursion and React component hierarchy.
- Assisted students with the debugging process, and taught them how to utilize documentation resources such as MDN docs and W3Schools.

2016 - 2018 | Chegg Tutors

#### **Tutor**

Same services and ratings as above, with a greater focus on drop-in students rather than pre-scheduled lessons.

2013 - 2017 | Robert Half (The Creative Group)

## **Web Developer Contractor**

- Took contract work for a variety of different clients, including Cascade Designs, Envision Telephony, and Williams-
- Built, edited, and debugged professional websites using PHP, C#, MySQL, HTML, CSS, and Javascript.
- Learned C# on the job at Envision and assisted other team members to do the same over the span of less than four months.

2011 - 2012 | Gage Design

## Web Developer

- Built, edited, and debugged professional websites using PHP, C#, MySQL, HTML, CSS, and Javascript.
- Collaborated with designers and the senior developer to ensure good functionality and SEO-friendliness.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Smith College**

Graduated 2011

B.A. in Computer Science

#### CONTACT



**509-308-5094** 



